Actually, sir, this "Detached castling"
strategy you were using
is more commonly
known as "Kokoriko."
It's one I came up with myself,
about 10 years ago.
I was so happy that a fool
like me could still give birth
seeing my dead baby
come back to life.
[King scoffs]
Rubbish.
I've lost interest. Take a break.
[Komugi] Huh?
[King] once we begin again…
Huh?
…you will not get any more breaks,
so be prepared.
[singer singing in English]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[upbeat music playing]
RESOLVE X AND X AWAKENING
[thunder rumbling]
[King] I don't like it.
During our matches,
my rhythm is the one
being disrupted, not hers.
By all rights, this should be
an unbearable indignity,
and yet, although I find
myself frustrated,
Huh?
[tense music playing]
[King] How vile.
She shows no signs
of intelligence or dignity.
How do those beautiful plays,
those paragons of logic
Nine-five-one, king.
[King] let's make a bet.
did you say, "bet"?
[King] I did.
If you win,
I swear that I will give you
anything your heart desires.
Anything? Let me see.
However…
Huh?
If you lose to me,
I'll take your left arm.
[rain pattering]
[thunder rumbling]
[King] Greed and fear
disrupt human rhythm.
Greed will cloud the eyes,
and fear, fear will cause
courage to shrivel and die.
I bet my life.
but I really
don't want to offend you
right after you made me
such a very generous offer.
But I still don't understand.
Explain yourself.
Whatever do you mean by that?
hardly make any money at all,
even national champions.
To become
a national representative,
you have to win
whole tournaments.
That means
that losing even one match
is enough to disqualify you.
It's just what my parents
have always said.
On the day that I set my sights
on playing Gungi professionally,
I told myself that I'd die
if I ever lost a match.
every second I've got
just thinking about Gungi.
[King] She feels neither fear nor greed.
[chuckles]
[laughing]
that I was the one
who lacked resolve!
-Huh?
-[King] I never imagined
Please, I would never,
ever do such a thing!
The thought never once
crossed my mind! I promise!
-[King] I know that.
-[sighs]
This is a personal matter.
No more betting.
That was my mistake.
[gasps]
So forgive me.
[stammers]
Sire! [gasps]
What have you done?
[Shaiapouf] Sire, please,
we must stop the bleeding!
[upbeat music playing]
[King] You heard me.
I said we'll continue playing.
I told you that there would be
no more breaks, did I not?
I am certain you will
still be able to play, sire,
even as your arm
is being reattached.
That is the biggest concession
I can make.
And if you refuse to accept
my offer, take my head
so that I may not live
with the shame of your death.
[whimpering]
Fine, then.
Come closer,
and I will end you with a single strike.
It's your turn to play, so move.
[Komugi] I won't.
I refuse to play
until your arm is better.
I'm very sorry.
I won't say it again. Now move.
I will not.
If you still wish to kill me,
do it in Gungi.
[crying]
You little-- [groans]
Summon Pitou!
Sire.
[crying]
[thunder rumbling]
[Morel] There's no doubt.
[Knov] All the puppets are gone.
Have they resumed
the sorting process again?
Doubtful. I would be very surprised.
so they wouldn't go
too far from his side.
Then what's going on?
[Knov] It shouldn't be.
They would if the king
had ordered it, wouldn't they?
I suppose so.
But regardless,
they've already retracted
their long-range
radar detection.
While we can, we have to get
as close as possible.
If we want this plan to succeed,
I must create an exit
near the palace.
We'll have to take this risk
sooner or later.
The time is now.
[Leol] There. I found them.
Just don't die.
The same to you, Morel.
[Leol chuckles]
Good. They've split up.
[chuckles]
[Neferpitou] Dr. Blythe.
[Neferpitou] Hmm. I'd say about two
or three hours to fix it completely.
[Shaiapouf] And you can't use
your puppets or En during that time?
Mm, this ability
takes an awful lot of Nen, meow.
Since it requires
quite a bit of your energy
Either way,
this is an important task
I cannot trust to anyone else.
[Knov] There's no evidence
they're using En.
We need an exit near the palace,
but if I'm spotted, it's all over.
While I can freely
come and go as I please,
Shoot and the others
can only use the exit to leave
once they enter the mansion.
I need to prepare three exits--
near, far, and in the middle.
That will help us
to keep a close eye on things.
When the time comes,
Once that has been determined,
we'll act.
From the enemy's perspective,
we'll seem to appear
before their very eyes.
I feel more dead than alive.
But I have a long way to go.
Should I wait for the sun to set?
That would be ideal, but will
the rain hold out until then?
[groans] I have no choice.
Should Neferpitou's En be reactivated,
any approach
will be all but impossible.
Even if I fail,
we still have other options.
Go without fear. Closer.
[thunder rumbling]
[narrator] Currently in the palace,
there are only three humans
the ants do not intend to eat.
First is the Gungi player,
the second is Diego,
and all dealings with foreign parties
and domestic organizations
went through him.
This puts him in the unique position
of being irreplaceable,
[narrator] There is not a single
human guard
posted anywhere near the palace.
Because ordinary soldiers would
be powerless against Nen users,
the royal guard determined that
the presence of human soldiers
would increase the risk
of enemy infiltration.
Cheetu, who has only just returned,
is the only squadron leader
on the premises,
the various squadron leaders'
personal favorites, and as such,
and his squadron leaders
has vanished entirely.
Self-interest was the only thing
keeping them there,
nothing more.
and are expected
to end in failure.
Lookout duty would never
be entrusted to the others.
but his current attempt
to infiltrate the palace
to provide at least three more staffers
to handle the secretarial duties,
I'll die of overwork for sure.
[sighs]
[computer chimes]
Huh?
SENDING YOU A LIST
REGARDING FRESH MEAT
[tense music playing]
Huh?
[laughs]
[gasps]
"Sinker Bell."
Yes.
PER OUR ARRANGEMENT,
I REQUEST NUMBERS 2, 16, 79, 103, AND 119
Hey, Palm, got a hit.
[closing theme music playing]
Palm is preparing to launch
an infiltration of her own.
[singer singing in Japanese]
And look
who's joining me today!
[Knov] Why am I here?
[Gon] Because Killua's not around.
-[Knov] Scream.
-[Gon screams]
[singer singing in Japanese]